Why not me?
What's that smell?
Prelude to Water Melody.
Who's there?
Don't kill me.
I beg you.
Don't kill...
Spare me.
Deputy Zhang!
Please, have mercy!
Young Marshal!
Young Madam!
What's going on?
Stay calm.
Go find Deputy Li
and have him handle Deputy Zhang.
Keep the details under wraps.
Yes.
Don't force yourself.
Let me help you inside.
Young Madam,
Young Marshal
is fine.
Just a severe knee sprain.
I've immobilized it
and applied oil to reduce bruising.
But
he can't move well now.
He needs rest.
I'll go to Hongji Hall
to get some good medicine.
No.
You can't go there.
Why?
It's the best pharmacy in Yang City.
That's why
you can't go there.
Chu Nanfeng runs the place.
If you go for medicine,
he'll know you're injured
and can't move freely.
At this critical juncture,
his injuries
must not be disclosed.
Then,
where can we get good medicine?
Xue,
go
to the Hongji Hall in my name.
Just say
I sprained my ankle yesterday
and need some medicine.
That way, it won't raise suspicion.
Yes, My Lady.
Deputy Li,
when we came in,
was there anything unusual?
Miss Ye Jinrou came by,
but I stopped her.
She was going to a shop
to get some rouge.
To get rouge?
She must be trying to send a message.
Let's go.
Check the yard again.
My Lady,
there's one more thing.
Take a look at this.
It was found on Deputy Zhang.
It's in the inner pocket.
He seems to have been drugged.
He's in a daze,
unable to recall anything.
He lost his memory?
In a daze?
He must have been poisoned by Ghost Vine.
This matter
must be kept confidential.
The most urgent task
is to stabilize Young Marshal's condition
and purge the traitor.
Yes.
Look carefully with your eyes.
This is Miss Ye.
How dare you stop me?
To Miss Cuijuan,
this is the order of the young madam.
Without the young madam's instruction,
no one can enter or leave the mansion.
Where are you going, Miss Ye?
Miss Su,
I just want to go to
to buy some cosmetics.
Why did you ask the servant
to stop me?
Are you really going to buy cosmetics,
or are you trying to send a message?
Miss Su,
what are you
coming to see me for?
You always pride yourself on being smart.
Why are you so evasive today?
Fine,
Let me be clear.
You had Cuijuan
poison my medicine,
and sent killers after the Young Marshal.
Dare you say
you didn't do these things?
What are you talking about?
No evidence,
don't just accuse people without proof.
This powder,
known as the best in the world, Prelude to Water Melody,
It contains ambergris,
musk,
agarwood.
The fragrance
can last for three months.
But this is the only box
in Yang City.
Miss Ye,
you have this fragrance on you.
I remember that day,
when I asked Cuijuan
to send a letter to Chu Nanfeng,
I specially
put this spice on the letter.
Cuijuan told me that day
that my cousin and I just met by chance.
I never opened that letter.
Did I say that this spice
was sprinkled on the letter paper?
I...
You...
Why are you silent?
Fine.
I'll tell you.
In Cuijuan's statement,
she said
she happened to meet you and the Young Marshal.
You didn't open the letter.
Then why
do both of you
have the scent on you?
You're slinging mud at me.
I don't know
what you're
talking about.
I don't know anything.
Don't set me up here.
Slinging mud at me?
Miss Ye,
if you never opened the letter,
why do you
have the scent of Prelude to Water Melody?
If you've never met the killer,
why does he
have the same smell?
Miss Ye,
do you still want to lie?
I want to talk to you alone.
Young Madam, no.
It's too dangerous.
It's okay.
You guys wait here.
Yes.
Do you know what I'm praying for?
It's just something external.
What I'm praying for is
that the Buddha blesses
the Ye family
to be completely gone.
What you just said
were all done by me.
I know.
Don't pretend to be a saint.
You're such a fake!
Su Muwan,
do you think I like doing those things?
Do you think
I want to stay in this mansion
that's like a cage,
watching you two being intimate,
and you showing off your title
as the wife of the Young Marshal?
You don't understand at all.
Even if
your family has fallen,
you were once the apple of their eye.
They truly loved you
and cared for you.
As for me,
to the Ye family,
I'm just a decoration,
an object.
I'm just a tool
to pave the way for my good-for-nothing brother
in the Ye family.
I'm not even as good as a dog in Ye family.
So,
this is your reason for hiring killers.
Because you are not satisfied with Ye family,
you want to use the lives of me and the young marshal
to fill your dissatisfaction?
Or what?
Do you really think I have any feelings
for Ling Shenxing?
That's ridiculous.
Love is the most useless thing
to me.
No matter how good he is in your eyes,
in my eyes,
he is just a buyer
carefully selected by the Ye family for me.
He is just
a backing
that allows me to take a breath
in front of the Ye family.
Su Muwan,
I don't want to kill you.
I really don't.
But you're in my way.
If you don't die,
Ling Shenxing will never see me.
I'll always be
the most useless person in the Ye Family.
They'll force me
to do more disgusting things.
I don't want to.
Only when you die,
can I be qualified
to take over the position.
Only then,
can I be of some value to the Ye family.
This is the marriage certificate
prepared by Old Madam Ling
for Ling Shenxing's remarriage.
From beginning to end,
your name is not on it.
How much
have you and the Old Madam
taken from the Lings?
The General and the Young Marshal know it well.
Even if I'm not the Young Marshal's wife,
you'll never be
the Young Marshal's wife.
Do you want to
trade our lives for your breathing space?
You poisoned me,
framed the Sus,
and sent people
to kill the Young Marshal.
Ye Jinrou,
your heart
has been drowned in the mire of the Ye family.
Yes.
Since the day I was sent
to the Young Marshal's Mansion as a gift,
my life has been immersed in the mire.
Tell me,
did I have a choice?
I was born into the Ye family,
and I'm a woman.
Did I have a choice?
My life
has never been my own.
The Ye family won't let me go,
and they won't let you go either.
We are both pitiful.
You had choices,
but you chose the most vicious
and unforgivable path.
The Ye family's preference for sons
is their sin,
but that's not a reason
for you to become a murderer.
Yes,
I am deeply sinful.
But I...
My sins are unforgivable.
You took poison?
Deputy Li,
hurry!
Young Madam!
Prepare the car for the hospital!
Yes!
Why do you save me?
It's the judge's job
to try you.
I'm a doctor.
A doctor's job
is to save lives.